<resources>
    <string name="app_name">iFeelings</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="send_button_label">Send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_image_test">ImageTest</string>

    <string name="text1">The museum is housed in the Louvre Palace, originally built as a fortress in the late 12th century…</string>
    <string name="text2">Gwanghwamun is the main and largest gate of Gyeongbokgung Palace, in Jongno-gu, Seoul, South Korea.</string>
    <string name="text3">Tower Bridge is a combined bascule and suspension bridge in London built in 1886–1894.</string>
    <string name="text4">The Temple of Heaven is an imperial complex of religious buildings situated in the southeastern part…</string>
    <string name="text5">The Aegean Islands are within the sea and some bound it on its southern periphery…</string>

    <string name="description1">American politician who served as the 44th President of the United States from 2009 to 2017. He is the first African American to have served as president. He previously served in the U.S. Senate representing Illinois from 2005 to 2008, and in the Illinois State Senate from 1997 to 2004.  Obama was born in Honolulu, Hawaii, two years after the territory was admitted to the Union as the 50th state. Raised largely in Hawaii, Obama also spent one year of his childhood in Washington State and four years in Indonesia. After graduating from Columbia University in 1983, he worked as a community organizer in Chicago. In 1988 Obama enrolled in Harvard Law School, where he was the first black president of the Harvard Law Review. After graduation, he became a civil rights attorney and professor, teaching constitutional law at the University of Chicago Law School from 1992 to 2004. Obama represented the 13th District for three terms in the Illinois Senate from 1997 to 2004, when he ran for the U.S. Senate. Obama received national attention in 2004, with his unexpected March primary win, his well-received July Democratic National Convention keynote address, and his landslide November election to the Senate. In 2008, Obama was nominated for president, a year after his campaign began, and after a close primary campaign against Hillary Clinton. He was elected over Republican John McCain, and was inaugurated on January 20, 2009. Nine months later, Obama was named the 2009 Nobel Peace Prize laureate.  During his first two years in office, Obama signed many landmark bills. Main reforms were the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act (often referred to as \"Obamacare\"), the Dodd–Frank Wall Street Reform and Consumer Protection Act, and the Don\'t Ask, Don\'t Tell Repeal Act of 2010. The American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009 and Tax Relief, Unemployment Insurance Reauthorization, and Job Creation Act of 2010 served as economic stimulus amidst the Great Recession, but the GOP regained control of the House of Representatives in 2011. After a lengthy debate over the national debt limit, Obama signed the Budget Control and the American Taxpayer Relief Acts. In foreign policy, Obama increased U.S. troop levels in Afghanistan, reduced nuclear weapons with the U.S.-Russian New START treaty, and ended military involvement in the Iraq War. He ordered military involvement in Libya in opposition to Muammar Gaddafi, and the military operation that resulted in the death of Osama bin Laden.</string>
    <string name="description2">United States from 2009 to 2017. He is the first African American to have served as president. He previously served in the U.S. Senate representing Illinois from 2005 to 2008, and in the Illinois State Senate from 1997 to 2004.  Obama was born in Honolulu, Hawaii, two years after the territory was admitted to the Union as the 50th state. Raised largely in Hawaii, Obama also spent one year of his childhood in Washington State and four years in Indonesia. After graduating from Columbia University in 1983, he worked as a community organizer in Chicago. In 1988 Obama enrolled in Harvard Law School, where he was the first black president of the Harvard Law Review. After graduation, he became a civil rights attorney and professor, teaching constitutional law at the University of Chicago Law School from 1992 to 2004. Obama represented the 13th District for three terms in the Illinois Senate from 1997 to 2004, when he ran for the U.S. Senate. Obama received national attention in 2004, with his unexpected March primary win, his well-received July Democratic National Convention keynote address, and his landslide November election to the Senate. In 2008, Obama was nominated for president, a year after his campaign began, and after a close primary campaign against Hillary Clinton. He was elected over Republican John McCain, and was inaugurated on January 20, 2009. Nine months later, Obama was named the 2009 Nobel Peace Prize laureate.  During his first two years in office, Obama signed many landmark bills. Main reforms were the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act (often referred to as \"Obamacare\"), the Dodd–Frank Wall Street Reform and Consumer Protection Act, and the Don\'t Ask, Don\'t Tell Repeal Act of 2010. The American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009 and Tax Relief, Unemployment Insurance Reauthorization, and Job Creation Act of 2010 served as economic stimulus amidst the Great Recession, but the GOP regained control of the House of Representatives in 2011. After a lengthy debate over the national debt limit, Obama signed the Budget Control and the American Taxpayer Relief Acts. In foreign policy, Obama increased U.S. troop levels in Afghanistan, reduced nuclear weapons with the U.S.-Russian New START treaty, and ended military involvement in the Iraq War. He ordered military involvement in Libya in opposition to Muammar Gaddafi, and the military operation that resulted in the death of Osama bin Laden.</string>
    <string name="url1">https://firebasestorage.googleapis.com/v0/b/friendlychat-10420.appspot.com/o/audio%2FDoor%20de%20ogen%20van%20Van%20Gogh%20in%20Nieuw-Amsterdam.mp3?alt=media&amp;token=c8309d36-e0d4-43c7-a6e6-49b9e4e76442</string>
    <string name="url2">http://www.mfiles.co.uk/mp3-downloads/edvard-grieg-peer-gynt1-morning-mood-piano.mp3</string>
    <string name="description3">我還記得那一年初夏我們在那棵老下約了定，我還記得她的臉龐，因為她不曾離開過我的心中，只是時光荏苒
    都我在看到她的時候，卻忘卻了當初的美好和許許多多的回憶，於是我們再續約重圓，希望還能見到最初的她，最初的我。只是月光還是當日圓
    能夠看見她的美好，才能看破鏡，回到當初那個小樹下，牽牽她的手，看看的臉龐，抱抱她，跟她說我都在，回來吧！人生可長，可短，只要你在。</string>

    <string name="sample">唐從聖出生於臺南縣永康市「影劇三村」。[2]
        後來，他曾在國立藝術學院取得戲劇學學士學位，並在銘傳大學取得傳播管理碩士學位。
        2000年，他經由朱延平提拔以「陳阿匾」一角演出於八大綜合台的政治戲仿節目《主席有約》，並以其模仿時任總統的陳水扁之演出受到關注。隨後，他在中天電視演出於《全民大悶鍋》、《全民最大黨》、《瘋狂大悶鍋》等節目，並以模仿李敖、陳水扁、鄭進一、李炳輝、彭華幹著稱。
        2013年11月1日，他發行個人首張微專輯《雙從人格》。
        2014年6月8日，他自銘傳大學取得傳播碩士學位。2017年6月21日被鏡周刊報導已有妻子及兩名小女兒的唐從聖，傳出與已有未婚夫且論及婚嫁的台大女護士外遇交往2017年9月26日 在《天才衝衝衝》節目錄影中，唐從聖多次吐槽徐乃麟「輸不起」，而遭到徐乃麟的辱罵。 9月29日，工作人員將事發影片翻拍並上傳至爆料公社後引起爭議。而後唐從聖於30日凌晨3時於臉書直播，表示因徐乃麟以連珠炮的五字經辱罵方式「問候母親」長達3分鐘，以致78歲的老母親受辱，預計將在10月初提出告訴。
    孫中山（1866年11月12日－1925年3月12日[註 1]），名文，幼名帝象，譜名德明，字載之，號日新、逸仙，室號品蘭堂。生於大清帝國廣東省廣州府香山縣翠亨村，祖籍廣東省紫金縣。清末民初醫師、政治家、革命家，是中華民國開國元勳，亦是中國國民黨之創黨人。流亡日本時，曾化名中山樵[4]:2936（日文平假名：なかやま きこり），在日本多尊稱其為中山先生，「中山」實為姓，惟後訛傳為「孫中山」，孫氏個人多用「孫文」或「孫逸仙」簽署重要文件，罕用「孫中山」。1905年，在日本東京組成中國同盟會，被推為總理[4]:2936；確定「驅除韃虜，恢復中華，建立民國，平均地權」[4]:2936政綱，提出三民主義學說[4]:2936。在日本東京由黑龍會領袖內田良平的號招下與華興會以及光復會等組織籌備成立中國同盟會，後於東京黑龍會總部組成中國同盟會，孫文主張使用狀似日本軍旗「旭日旗」的「青天白日旗」，反對使用黃興所提出的井字旗作為革命旗幟，並在黑龍會等組織的支持下被推為總理。1911年12月29日，被十七省代表在南京推選為中華民國臨時大總統，1912年1月1日在南京宣布就職，建立中華民國臨時政府[4]:2936。1919年，將中華革命黨改組為中國國民黨[4]:29361940年4月，國民政府明令尊稱孫中山先生為中華民國國父[5]。中國共產黨尊其為「中國近代民主革命的偉大先行者」[4]:2936[6]。
孫文童年曾受太平天國的影響，就有革命思想。但到了青年時期，他依舊未有行動，只期望進入官場，28歲上書清朝重臣李鴻章，建言改革，卻遭遇李的冷落[7]。日本命令將兵遣師，侵入中國[8]:52。1894年11月24日，孫文在檀香山成立興中會（中國國民黨前身）[9]:52。1895年，興中會發動乙未廣州起義[9]:53。
原本，孫文提倡以武裝革命推翻滿清統治以建立中華民國，但民國建立以後，他得不到北洋軍人的信任、支持，所以他又提倡武力推翻中華民國北洋政府，於是遭受許多非議。他提出三民主義等政治綱領，影響中國政治至深，中國國民黨建立的政權繼承他的黨國體制和以黨治軍思想[10]，尊其為唯一總理。</string>
</resources>
